export const data = [
    {
      "id": 0,
      "question": "They come out at night without being called, and are lost in the day without being stolen. What are they?",
      "answer": "stars"
    },
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "I'm full of holes but still hold water. What am I?",
      "answer": "sponge"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "I have legs but can't walk, a strong back but can't work,two good arms but can't reach, I have a seat but can't sit.",
      "answer": "chair"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "I am made of water, but Iâ€™m not wet.What am I?",
      "answer": "cloud"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Four legs up, four legs down, soft in the middle, hard all around.What am I?",
      "answer": "bed"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Two twins live together all the time. They see the whole world, but never see each other.",
      "answer": "eyes"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "I use my ear to speak and my mouth to hear. What am I?",
      "answer": "phone"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "I can carry lots of food, but cannot eat anything. What am I?",
      "answer": "fridge"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "When it comes to me, you go on red and stop on green. What am I?",
      "answer": "watermelon"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "What word begins and ends with an E but only has one letter?",
      "answer": "envelope"
    }
]